{
  "uniqueId": 4,
  "name": "Katakana Reading Quiz",
  "article": "a",
  "category": "Kana",
  "instructions":"Type the reading of the below word in Romaji!",
  "showDictionaryLink": false,
  "cards": [
    {"question":"ア","answer":["a"]},
    {"question":"イ","answer":["i"]},
    {"question":"ウ","answer":["u"]},
    {"question":"エ","answer":["e"]},
    {"question":"オ","answer":["o"]},
    {"question":"カ","answer":["ka"]},
    {"question":"キ","answer":["ki"]},
    {"question":"ク","answer":["ku"]},
    {"question":"ケ","answer":["ke"]},
    {"question":"コ","answer":["ko"]},
    {"question":"サ","answer":["sa"]},
    {"question":"シ","answer":["shi"]},
    {"question":"ス","answer":["su"]},
    {"question":"セ","answer":["se"]},
    {"question":"ソ","answer":["so"]},
    {"question":"タ","answer":["ta"]},
    {"question":"チ","answer":["chi"]},
    {"question":"ツ","answer":["tsu"]},
    {"question":"テ","answer":["te"]},
    {"question":"ト","answer":["to"]},
    {"question":"ナ","answer":["na"]},
    {"question":"ニ","answer":["ni"]},
    {"question":"ヌ","answer":["nu"]},
    {"question":"ネ","answer":["ne"]},
    {"question":"ノ","answer":["no"]},
    {"question":"ハ","answer":["ha", "wa"]},
    {"question":"ヒ","answer":["hi"]},
    {"question":"フ","answer":["fu", "hu"]},
    {"question":"ヘ","answer":["he", "e"]},
    {"question":"ホ","answer":["ho"]},
    {"question":"マ","answer":["ma"]},
    {"question":"ミ","answer":["mi"]},
    {"question":"ム","answer":["mu"]},
    {"question":"メ","answer":["me"]},
    {"question":"モ","answer":["mo"]},
    {"question":"ヤ","answer":["ya"]},
    {"question":"ユ","answer":["yu"]},
    {"question":"ヨ","answer":["yo"]},
    {"question":"ラ","answer":["ra"]},
    {"question":"リ","answer":["ri"]},
    {"question":"ル","answer":["ru"]},
    {"question":"レ","answer":["re"]},
    {"question":"ロ","answer":["ro"]},
    {"question":"ワ","answer":["wa"]},
    {"question":"ヲ","answer":["wo", "o"]},
    {"question":"キャ","answer":["kya"]},
    {"question":"キュ","answer":["kyu"]},
    {"question":"キョ","answer":["kyo"]},
    {"question":"シャ","answer":["sha"]},
    {"question":"シュ","answer":["shu"]},
    {"question":"ショ","answer":["sho"]},
    {"question":"チャ","answer":["cha"]},
    {"question":"チュ","answer":["chu"]},
    {"question":"チョ","answer":["cho"]},
    {"question":"ニャ","answer":["nya"]},
    {"question":"ニュ","answer":["nyu"]},
    {"question":"ニョ","answer":["nyo"]},
    {"question":"ヒャ","answer":["hya"]},
    {"question":"ヒュ","answer":["hyu"]},
    {"question":"ヒョ","answer":["hyo"]},
    {"question":"リャ","answer":["rya"]},
    {"question":"リュ","answer":["ryu"]},
    {"question":"リョ","answer":["ryo"]},
    {"question":"ン","answer":["n"]}
]}